Want to give magic a try?
Yes!
I think it should be magic
that everyone will enjoy!
They were beautiful.
I want to be recognized as a great idol by all!
Once I do that, I know I can change the world!
Let's get it on!
Yeah, Toko's a hard one to shake.
Is this...
me?
Lulu, go out and sing!
I did it! I was brave!
I'm Lilly! Nice to meet you too!
So hot!
You're kidding.
No good! No good!
What now? What now?
Summer means sea,
and we've got our own private beach!
It's only natural we swim!
Th-There's no way this is just a prank.
Please help me save everyone!
What was that?
A song me and big sis made together.
...Because you really wanted to have it
with the person you love.
I think you're pretty honest, Lilly-san.
Talking with you really cheered me up.
Thanks!
Nice fresh air!
I'm the cat here!
I think everyone wants to see you
singing the way you usually do.
Lililula palilula!
Could this be someone's magic?
LuluttoLilly
Lead the materials over there!
Got it!
How's the stage coming along?
It's getting there!
Good to hear!
The Festival of Magic is almost upon us!
La-la-la-la, dam-da
Di-di-ta-ta, di-di-ta
Chant the spell slowly
Wrap yourself in a secret
Logic overflowing around
Let's blow it all away
My daily routine's getting boring
But when I met you it started swingin'
The time began to fly
Enjoying the nightlife, my heart racing
There's no stopping this dream
Hey, come over here
Swingin' magic
Don't leave me
Just dance the way you feel
And the joy will only grow
Oh, wow, oh, wow
Swingin' magic
Di-di-ta-ta-di-di-ta
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Swingin' magic
Secret Message
Ready? I'm starting it.
Yep, I'm ready!
VOLUME
CHANNEL
HOME
APPS
GUIDE
MENU
OK
LuluttoLilly - 1st Live @ZeppoCity
LuluttoLilly
It's starting!
Our meeting was no coincidence
We're like two stars connected in a constellation
Could you really be Lilly-san?
One Hour Earlier
I'm so full.
Can Fuu use magic?
Aw, winter break's already over?
I've been studying so hard lately,
I could use a little breather.
Huh, weird hearing you say that, big sis.
I know! I'll watch the LuluttoLilly concert
I was excited for!
Huh?!
Want to watch it with me, Fuu?
Can I?
Thank you all very much!
Whew, that was fun!
By the way, when did you start to like Lilly-chan?
Huh?
Hmm, I can't remember.
Did you see her perform in Shibuya?
Oh, yeah, I did! You too?
Yes, on a livestream.
Wow, I didn't know!
And how about Lulu?
Lulu-chan...
I've been her fan since she made her debut.
LuluttoLilly - 1st Live @Zeppo City
@SHIBU★YEAHHH TEENS MEETING
CompatoLilly - Debut Concert!
MashuLulu - "Little singing bird" from
Happiness Music
Search
I see.
Lulu-chan is so mature and super cute!
You think so?
Yeah!
And she's such a hard worker too!
Huh?
LuluttoLilly - 1st Live @ZeppoCity
Search
She worked so hard on the dance for this concert.
Maybe too hard.
But that's why.
I mean, a friend told me that!
You know quite a lot.
Anything else?
Hm? That's it.
Just, she's amazing!
Fuu, can you come to the shop?
Okay!
Big sis, I'm happy we watched the concert together!
Talk to you later!
Something's not right.
Goodbye!
Oh, Sho-chan!
Morning!
Oh, morning, Fuu.
You look happy.
I am! Yesterday, my big sis and I...
watched the LuluttoLilly concert online!
Really?
Yeah!
So that's what it was.
You see, big sis has been a lot more chatty lately.
It feels like we're getting along
again like we used to!
You were getting along badly before?
Hmm... I wouldn't say badly.
It's complicated.
Greetings. Today marks a new semester,
New Semester
the last of fifth grade.
So stay on your best behavior
and keep working hard.
What'd you do for the New Year's?
I slept through it.
Hey, look at this!
What is it?
Show me!
Dat-dah!
LuluttoLilly merch?
That's so cool! Did you buy that?
I splurged on merch after the concert ended!
There was so much cute stuff!
Aww, lucky!
I can tell Fuu was hiding something from me yesterday.
I should investigate.
She comes down this way
from elementary school, right?
Found her!
Aww, another regular.
Time to give up?
I gotta get that golden one!
Which means...
Is she using magic?
I'll have to use all my New Year's money!
I got you, golden Kabappy!
Woo-hoo!
What is that...?
So cute!
I'm gonna take such good care of you!
I think Lilly-san is working today.
So she should be going to the agency next!
Wh-What a lovely wall!
Time to go home.
That was close...
This time she's going to use magic!
Ouch, that's hot!
Whoa, you're going to burn yourself!
Drink some water.
Are you okay?
She didn't use magic at all.
Fuu
Coming.
Big sis?
I brought you some hot milk.
Thanks...
But why?
Umm...
It's cold today, so I was worried
you might freeze if the windows were broken.
The windows?
They're not broken...
No?
Th-That's good.
Fuu's room...
It's a mess.
Big sis?
It's nothing.
Stay warm, okay?
Good night.
Okay.
So you were just worried
since it's cold.
Good night, big sis!
Once More
Did I get the wrong idea?
Azuki, you gave me the powers to use magic, right?
Yes!
Back then, I saw Lilly-san's performance
and wished to be able to sing again too.
That's right! And what a lovely wish it was.
Tell me...
did Fuu get powers too?
Huh?!
Do you know something, Azuki?
Nuh—No–thing?
Really?
Hey, Uguisu!
Wake up! It's an emergency!
What is it...?
Rui is suspicious of Fuu!
For what?
She might've caught on to her magic!
Oh no! She can't find out!
What do we do?
We have to trick her!
Yes we do!
Yes, yes.
Let's go to sleep.
So sweepy.
Aight.
All ready.
Is the new recruit starting today?
Yep. Said it just had to be our agency.
Had to be? That's odd.
What's that supposed to mean, Prez?
Right, sorry.
Go get her all the gigs you can.
No can do, I've got games to catch up on.
Ugh, please focus.
So this is Production Once More...
What'cha doing?
Um, h-hello!
You're Araki Asahi-chan, correct?
Yep, that's me.
Let's give it our all today!
I'm cold...
Alright, coast is clear.
Time to transform.
Litto!
Lililula palilula!
Pam pam power!
Wow...
So Lilly-chan does love Kabappy!
Just like her profile says!
I'm actually breathing
the same air as her! My gosh!
I wish I could take this air with me!
Toko, are you sure about this girl?
It might not seem like it,
but I think she's got great potential.
Hmm...
Documents are all clear.
Asahi. Can't wait to work with you.
Sena-sama! I look forward to it too!
Are you already familiar with our agency?
Y-Yes! Very familiar.
I see.
Is there anything you want to do here? Any goals?
Anything I want to do? This is sudden...
You want to be an idol, right?
Don't worry 'bout it.
It's a tough question to answer on the spot.
Good morning!
Morning, Lilly!
Lilly, allow me to introduce you!
This is Araki Asahi-chan. She just joined today!
A newbie!
I'm Lilly! Glad to have you!
N-No, th-that's okay.
If we shake hands I might die!
The building's kinda scary and worn-down,
but don't worry, everyone here is friendly!
R-Really?
And Café Dubdub next door
has the most delicious parfait!
So cute.
Worn-down building, she says.
At least it's close to the station.
Alright, I'll be on my way.
I might have some time,
but I can't idle about.
Good work.
Good morning!
Hey. We have a new recruit today.
Today, you say?
Um, where's Lilly?
She's with the rest. I'll leave her to you.
Take care!
MOURI
BUILDING
NO. 1
I haven't seen Lilly-san since the concert.
But if Fuu really can transform like me...
What do I do?
Hey, talking about parfaits made me hungry!
We're not getting takeout today.
What?
Sena-san, you're hungry too, right?
Nope.
Liar!
So can we get magical scones?
Still no!
That's no fair!
You're all amazing.
Back to the idol question...
I've been watching all of you
at Once More for a long time.
I saw your last concert too.
It made me feel like I couldn't
just sit watching, so I made my move.
Though I wanted to just keep watching you forever.
I see!
So we got through to you, Asahi-chan!
I'm so happy! This is what we work hard for!
Alright, then!
We've got our own recording of the concert!
Wanna watch?
Yes, absolutely!
If I see Lilly-san like this...
Let's do it, then.
Should I use magic to see for myself?
So excited!
Roll the tape.
You got it!
Lululila pululila.
Tell me the secret of the song from back then.
Our meeting was no coincidence
We're like two stars connected in a constellation
What on earth?!
If we happen to connect with one another
So cool!
Then we'd know now
Is this the newest tech?
Awesome!
That it was a miracle
Let's combine our feelings
Synchronize our heartbeats
No, not this song!
And let our imaginations grow even wilder
(UFO, take us away)
I want to know more about our song
from my memories!
If we fall in love (We'll soar into the sky)
Magical
Even the dreams I cannot reach
So long as you're with me, I can make them happen
Universe
Please stay with me, don't leave
"We'll soar into the sky"?
We're gentle shooting stars, love
Was all that back then...?
Taking a rendezvous on a crescent moon
What was that just now?
That startled me.
The new tech is so cool.
What button did I press for that?
Oh, Lulu-chan?
Did you just get here?
Yes. Good morning.
Right, I gotta introduce you.
This is our new member, Asahi.
Whew, that was so cool!
The greatest concert ever!
Nice to meet you. I'm Lulu.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
L-L-Lulu-chan?!
H-Hello! It's my pleasure...
Glad to have you here!
My gosh!
LuluttoLilly is here!
The legendary unit is together!
Really, are you sure about her?
Umm... I think, yes.
Hello, Asahi-chan?
What's gotten into you?
Earth to Asahi-chan!
In the end, I couldn't figure out
what that song was about.
If Lilly-san really is Fuu...
what should I do?
Et cetera cera...
Here and there things go as God says
But that's boring
So if I make my own decisions
All around me will start moving
If you peer into the heart of a passerby
Whatever their dream is, it shines like a jewel
Precious heart
Take the pieces of dreams scattered around the world
Line them all up
And make it come true on three, it'll be amazing
Dreams à la mode, for you
I'll make our planet into a great big dessert
As long as we have hope, we'll be OK
We'll be OK
Dreams à la mode, for you
I'm sure there's colorful, sweet spells in store
Try believing it, and tomorrow will be a good day
La la la, now we're smiling together, see you in the future
The Magic Songstress